Guide to the E. Ethelbert Miller papers, 1936-2021, bulk 1962-2018 MS2215
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Ethelbert Miller materials, 1962-2018; 1940-2021; Series 1; Miller, E. Ethelbert
  - Poet files, 1969-2009; 1969-2020; Series 1 Subseries 2
    - Lewis, William Henry: correspondence, works by, 1996 (Box 38, Folder 3)
    - Lights, Rikki: promotional material, correspondence, works by, 1977-1982 (Box 38, Folder 4)
    - Lilley, Gary: works by, undated (Box 38, Folder 5)
    - Lilley, Gary: correspondence, cirriculum vitae, 1996-1999 (Box 38, Folder 6)
    - Lindsay, 1978; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 97, Folder 9)
    - Lindsey, Kay, Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 97, Folder 10)
    - Lipsitz, Lou, 1991; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 97, Folder 11)
    - Liu, Lily, 1998-1999; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 97, Folder 12)
    - Llewellyn, Chris, 1981-1990; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 97, Folder 13)
    - Locke, Alain Leroy, Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 97, Folder 14)
    - Loizeaux, William, 1973, 1997-1998; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 97, Folder 15)
    - Lolly, Michael, 1995; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 97, Folder 16)
    - Longfellow, Henry, 1886, 2001, 2007; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 97, Folder 17)
    - Lorde, Audrey: interviews, correspondence, 1981-1990 (Box 38, Folder 7)
    - Lorde, Audrey: profiles, articles, 1979-1991 (Box 38, Folder 8)
    - Lorde, Audrey: reviews, 1996-2002 (Box 38, Folder 9)
    - Love, Monifa A., 1994, 1996; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 97, Folder 18)
    - Lovelace, Earl, 1997; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 97, Folder 19)
    - Lowe, Lorna, 1993, 1996; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 97, Folder 20)
    - Lowe, Morgan, 1995; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 97, Folder 21)
    - Lyles, Charlise, 1993-2003; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 97, Folder 22)
    - Lynch, Charles H., 1986-1990; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 97, Folder 23)
    - Lynch, Gwendolyn, 1990; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 97, Folder 24)
    - Lynch, Janice: works by, correspondence [1 of 3], 1987-1992 (Box 38, Folder 10)
    - Lynch, Janice: works by, correspondence [2 of 3], 1987-1992 (Box 38, Folder 11)
    - Lynch, Janice: works by [3 of 3] (Box 38, Folder 12)
    - Lyon, George Ella, 1979; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 97, Folder 25)
    - MacKay, Terri, 1994; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 97, Folder 26)
    - Mackey, Nathaniel, 1996, 1999; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 97, Folder 27)
    - Madgett, Naomi Long, 1982, 1993; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 97, Folder 28)
    - Madhubuti, Haki: articles, reviews, 1978 (Box 38, Folder 13)
    - Madhubuti, Haki: interviews, 1972-1999 (Box 38, Folder 14)
    - Madhubuti, Haki: correspondence, undated (Box 38, Folder 15)
    - Madhubuti, Haki: works by, promotional material, 1985-1988 (Box 38, Folder 16)
    - Madhubuti, Haki: miscellaneous material, undated (Box 38, Folder 17)
    - Maggio, Mike, 2007; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 98, Folder 1)
    - Major, Clarence, 1976-1998; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 98, Folder 2)
    - Major, Devorah, 1995; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 98, Folder 3)
    - Maldonado, A. Juanita, 1987-1988; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 98, Folder 4)
    - Malone, Carol, 1994-1997; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 98, Folder 5)
    - M-A-N-C-O-L-I-A, 2004; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 191, Folder 4)
    - Manning, Cornell, 1995 March 16; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 98, Folder 6)
    - Maponya, Maishe, 1990-1992; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 98, Folder 7)
    - Marano, Dawn, 1995; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 98, Folder 8)
    - Marcus, Robin, 1982; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 98, Folder 9)
    - Markham, E.A., 1987, 1998-1999; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 98, Folder 10)
    - Marquez, Roberto, Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 98, Folder 11)
    - Marshall, Paul, Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 98, Folder 12)
    - Martin, Carl, 1997; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 98, Folder 13)
    - Martin, Christine D., 1984, 1990; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 98, Folder 14)
    - Martin, James H.N., 1993; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 98, Folder 15)
    - Martin, Regina: works by, 1994-1996 (Box 39, Folder 1)
    - Martin, Regina: reviews, 1994 (Box 39, Folder 2)
    - Martin, Regina: correspondence, 1995 (Box 39, Folder 3)
    - Martin, Renita, 1995-1996; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 98, Folder 16)
    - Martiniello, Marco, 1995; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 98, Floppy disk 17)
    - Marvin X, 1982-1983; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 98, Folder 18)
    - Masini, Donna: correspondence, works by (Box 39, Folder 4)
    - Maso, Carole, 1985-1992; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 98, Folder 19)
    - Mason, Ketih Antar, 1988-1992; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 98, Folder 20)
    - Massaquoi, Princess Fatima, Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 98, Folder 21)
    - Massey, Kenneth L., 2004; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 98, Folder 22)
    - Mataka, Laini, Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 98, Folder 23)
    - Mathis, Sharon Bell: clippings, press, 1984-1986 (Box 39, Folder 5)
    - Matthews, James David, Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 99, Folder 1)
    - Matthews, Valerie, Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 100, Folder 14)
    - Maurer, Harry, Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 99, Folder 2)
    - Mayfield, Juliana: promotional material, undated (Box 39, Folder 6)
    - Mayfield, Juliana: profiles, articles, 1975-1984 (Box 39, Folder 7)
    - Mayfield, Juliana: correspondence, 1984-1985 (Box 39, Folder 8)
    - Mayfield, Juliana: works by, undated (Box 39, Folder 9)
    - Mayfield, Juliana: obituaries, tributes, 1984 (Box 39, Folder 10)
    - Mayfield, Juliana: interviews, 1984 (Box 39, Folder 11)
    - Mayfield, Juliana: photogrpahs, undated (Box 39, Folder 12)
    - Mayfield, Juliana: biography, resume, 1983-1984 (Box 39, Folder 13)
    - Maynard, Dori J., 1995-1996; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 99, Folder 3)
    - Mberi, Antar, 1981; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 99, Folder 4)
    - McAleavey, David Willard: correspondence, 1985-1986 (Box 39, Folder 14)
    - McAnally, Mary, 1981, 1983; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 99, Folder 5)
    - McCall, Nathan, 1993-1994; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 124, Folder 12)
    - McCallum, Shara: promotional materials, 2002 (Box 39, Folder 15)
    - McCallum, Shara: works by, 1998-1999 (Box 39, Folder 16)
    - McCallum, Shara: correspondence, 1995-1997 (Box 39, Folder 17)
    - McCann, Richard, 2003; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 99, Folder 6)
    - McCanti, James, 1989; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 99, Folder 7)
    - McCarthy, Eugene: works by, 1997 (Box 40, Folder 1)
    - McCarriston, Linda, 1993-2000; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 124, Folder 13)
    - McCoy, Virginia W., 1983-1985; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 99, Folder 8)
    - McDaniel, Jeffrey, 1995 November 24; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 99, Folder 9)
    - McDonald, Ann, 1987; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 99, Folder 10)
    - McDonnell, Evelyn, 1994; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 99, Folder 11)
    - McDowell, Deborah: correspondence, 1996 (Box 40, Folder 2)
    - McDowell, Garrett, 1992; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 99, Folder 12)
    - McElroy, Colleen, 1977; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 99, Folder 13)
    - McGrath, Beth: correspondence, works by, 1989-1990 (Box 40, Folder 3)
    - McHugh, Heather, 2000 May; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 99, Folder 14)
    - McInnis, C. Leigh, 1999; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 99, Folder 15)
    - McKeever, Herman, 1976-1985; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 99, Folder 16)
    - McKnight, Jo-Anne, 1968; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 99, Folder 17)
    - McLemee, Scott, 1990-1995; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 99, Folder 18)
    - McMichael, Sam, Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 99, Folder 19)
    - McMillan, Terry: correspondence, 1985-1997 (Box 40, Folder 4)
    - McMillan, Terry: promotinal material, 1987-1992 (Box 40, Folder 5)
    - McRitchie, Elizabeth, Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 99, Folder 20)
    - McWhirten, Bea, 1982, 1985; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 99, Folder 21)
    - Meadows, Jerome, 1994; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 99, Folder 22)
    - Mealy, Rosemari, 1978-1980; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 99, Folder 23)
    - Meally, Marc, Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 99, Folder 24)
    - Medina, Tony, 1992 November 6; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 99, Folder 25)
    - Meek, Sandra, Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 100, Folder 1)
    - Meeker, Amanda Lee, Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 100, Folder 2)
    - MeLanson, Philip, 1988; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 100, Folder 3)
    - Melendez, Jesus Papoleto, 1991-1996; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 100, Folder 4)
    - Menga, Guy, Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 100, Folder 5)
    - Mengestu, Dinaw, 2007; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 100, Folder 6)
    - Merry, Marilyn, 1985; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 100, Folder 7)
    - Mervyn, Morris, 1981-1988; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 100, Folder 8)
    - Miscellaneous Poems/Publications, Undated; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 191, Folder 9)
    - Mills, David, 1994-1995; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 124, Folder 14)
    - Minkah, 1995; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 100, Folder 9)
    - Miranda, Samuel A.: works by, 1996-1997 (Box 40, Folder 6)
    - Misterka, Adam F., 1995; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 100, Folder 10)
    - Mitchell, Brian Stokes, 2007 January; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 100, Folder 11)
    - Mitchell, Felicia, 1994; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 100, Folder 12)
    - Mitchell, Rich, 1995; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 100, Folder 13)
    - Moldea, Dan: correspondence, 1982 (Box 40, Folder 7)
    - Moldea, Dan: reviews, 1989-1995 (Box 40, Folder 8)
    - Moldea, Dan: promotional material, 1989-1991 (Box 40, Folder 9)
    - Moldea, Dan: works by, 1984-1985 (Box 40, Folder 10)
    - Moldea, Dan: articles, 1988-2001 (Box 40, Folder 11)
    - Moldea, Dan: interviews, 1981-1982 (Box 40, Folder 12)
    - Moldea, Dan: miscellaneous, 1987-1994 (Box 40, Folder 13)
    - Montgomery, Candace Hill, 1981-1983; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 100, Folder 15)
    - Moomau, Glenn: correspondence, 1990 (Box 40, Folder 14)
    - Moon, C., 1987, 1992; MS2215 Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 200, Folder 8)
    - Moon, Charley, 1994; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 100, Folder 16)
    - Moore, Leonard: correspondence, promotional material, 1983-1995 (Box 40, Folder 15)
    - Moore, Leonard: works by, 1995-2004 (Box 40, Folder 16)
    - Moore, Leonard: correspondence, clippings, 1982-1993 (Box 40, Folder 17)
    - Moore, Leonard: correspondence, clippings, 1984-1994 (Box 41, Folder 1)
    - Moore, Leonard: correspondence, articles, 1995-2000 (Box 41, Folder 2)
    - Moore, Opal, 1995; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 100, Folder 21)
    - Morales, Aurora, 1991; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 100, Folder 17)
    - Morgan, Charles, 1997, 2007; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 100, Folder 18)
    - Morgenstern, Felicia, 1996-1999; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 100, Folder 19)
    - Morgenthaler, Sharon, 1984, 1988-1990; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 100, Folder 20)
    - Morris, Keith S., 1993-1995; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 100, Folder 22)
    - Morrison, Toni: "Beloved", 1998; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 101, Folder 10)
    - Morrison, Toni: Interviews, 1981-2001; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 101, Folder 11)
    - Morrison, Toni, Noble Prize, 1992-1999; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 101, Folder 12)
    - Morrison, Toni: Review, Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 101, Folder 13)
    - Morrison, Toni: "Tar Baby", 1981; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 101, Folder 14)
    - Morse, L.C., 1987-1988; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 100, Folder 23)
    - Mosely, Walter: book reviews, 1994-1998 (Box 41, Folder 3)
    - Mosley, Walter: profiles, 1995-1999 (Box 41, Folder 4)
    - Mosley, Walter: film review, 1995 (Box 41, Folder 5)
    - Mosely, Walter: programs, 1997 (Box 41, Folder 6)
    - Mosely, Walter: miscellaneous (Box 41, Folder 7)
    - Mosher, Marlene, 1975; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 100, Folder 24)
    - Mphahlele, Ezekiel, 1978, 1985; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 100, Folder 25)
    - Mrove, Haas H., Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 101, Folder 1)
    - Muckenhirn, Karen, 2005 May 13; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 172, Folder 7)
    - Muhammad, Askia, Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 101, Folder 2)
    - Muhammad, Askia, 1977-1984; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 175, Folder 1)
    - Muhammad, Donald, 1997, 1999; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 101, Folder 3)
    - Mungen, Donna, 1985-1988; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 101, Folder 4)
    - Muni, Kai, 1990-1991; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 101, Folder 5)
    - Mura, David, 1994-1995; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 101, Folder 6)
    - Murphy, Mariline, 1997; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 101, Folder 7)
    - Murray, Albert, 1985-1986, 2002; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 101, Folder 8)
    - Murry, Monifa, Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 101, Folder 9)
    - Naani, Karen, 1998 July 30; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 101, Folder 15)
    - Nakash, Mikail, 1989; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 101, Folder 16)
    - Napier, Winston, Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 101, Folder 17)
    - Nasir, Tania Tamari, 1995; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 101, Folder 18)
    - Nathan, Miriam, 1994, 1999; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 101, Folder 19)
    - Nathan, Miriam Morsel: works by, correspondence, 2002-2003 (Box 41, Folder 8)
    - Naylor, Gloria: articles, 1988-1994 (Box 41, Folder 9)
    - Naylor, Gloria: The Women of Brewster Place, 1983-1989 (Box 41, Folder 10)
    - Naylor, Gloria: Linden Hills, 1983-1985 (Box 41, Folder 11)
    - Naylor, Gloria: Mamas Day, 1988 (Box 41, Folder 12)
    - Naylor, Gloria: correspondence, lectures, promotional material (Box 41, Folder 13)
    - Neal, Gaston, 1971, 1996-1999; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 101, Folder 20)
    - Neal, Larry: Correspondence, 1977, 1984; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 102, Folder 1)
    - Neal, Larry: Interviews, 1977-1983; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 102, Folder 2)
    - Neal, Larry: Magazine Articles, 1981-1983; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 102, Folder 3)
    - Neal, Larry: Miscellaneous, 1982; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 102, Folder 4)
    - Neal, Larry: Programs and Promotional Material, 1983-2001; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 102, Folder 5)
    - Neal, Larry: Rap, 1991-1996; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 102, Folder 6)
    - Neal, Larry: Tributes and Obituaries, 1981; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 102, Folder 7)
    - Neal, Larry: Works By, 1968-1976; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 102, Folder 8)
    - Neely, Jessica, Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 102, Folder 9)
    - Nelson, David, 1990-1997; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 102, Folder 10)
    - Nelson, Jennifer: works by, 1991-2008 (Box 41, Folder 14)
    - Nelson, Maudine J., 1982-1989; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 102, Folder 11)
    - Nelson, Paul, 1994-1996; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 102, Folder 12)
    - Nicholson, David, 1979, 1985-1990; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 102, Folder 13)
    - Nicholson, David: works by, promotional material, 1986-1987 (Box 41, Folder 15)
    - Nielsen, A.L.: works by, correspondence, 1982-1997 (Box 41, Folder 16)
    - Nickelson, Chris, 1999; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 102, Folder 14)
    - Nickelson, Christopher, Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 102, Folder 15)
    - Ning, Tie, 1995; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 103, Folder 1)
    - Nordhaus, Jean: correspondence, works by, 1998 (Box 41, Folder 17)
    - Ntal-I'mbirwa, Alimasi, 1992; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 103, Folder 2)
    - Nuru, Njeri, 1981-1984; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 103, Folder 3)
    - Nye, Naomi Shihab, 1983-1989, 1995-1996; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 103, Folder 4)
    - Obeichina, Emmanuel, 1988; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 103, Folder 5)
    - Obradovic, Biljana D., 1999 July 1; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 103, Folder 6)
    - Oden, Gloria: correspondence, works by, 1964-1983 (Box 41, Folder 18)
    - Okai, Atukwei, 1971; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 103, Folder 7)
    - Okantah, Mwatabu S., 2003; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 103, Folder 8)
    - Okantah, Mwatbu: correspondence, clippings, 1982-1984 (Box 41, Folder 19)
    - Olds, Sharon, 1984; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 103, Folder 9)
    - Olinka, Sharon, 1995-1996; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 103, Folder 10)
    - Olinka, Sharron: correspondence, works by, promotional materials, 1989-1991 (Box 41, Folder 20)
    - O'Meally, Bob, 1976; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 103, Folder 11)
    - Oren, Michel, 1990; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 103, Folder 12)
    - Orfalea, Greg: correspondence, clippings, promotional material, 1985-1987 (Box 42, Folder 1)
    - Orion, Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 103, Folder 15)
    - Osbey, Brenda Marie, 1994-1999; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 103, Folder 13)
    - Osbey, Brenda M: biography, undated (Box 42, Folder 2)
    - Osbey, Brenda M.: works by [1 of 2] (Box 42, Folder 3)
    - Osbey, Brenda M.: works by [2 of 2] (Box 42, Folder 4)
    - Osbey, Brenda M.: correspondence, 1997 (Box 42, Folder 5)
    - Osbey, Brenda M.: post cards, photographs (Box 42, Folder 6)
    - Osbey, Brenda M.: promotional material, 1997 (Box 42, Folder 7)
    - Oyoko, 1976-1977; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 103, Folder 14)
    - Page, Alan C., 1995; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 103, Folder 16)
    - Pal, Sunanda, 1995; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 103, Folder 17)
    - Palmer, Ronald, 2001-2002; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 103, Folder 18)
    - Palmer, Ronald: works by, undated (Box 42, Folder 8)
    - Palmer, Terry, 1994; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 103, Folder 19)
    - Panchan, Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 103, Folder 20)
    - Parker, Gwendolyn, 1994-1995; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 103, Folder 21)
    - Parkerson, Michelle: promotional material, 1980-1987 (Box 42, Folder 9)
    - Parkerson, Michelle: profiles, articles, 1985-1987 (Box 42, Folder 10)
    - Parkerson, Michelle: correspondence, 1977-1987 (Box 42, Folder 11)
    - Parkerson, Michelle: interviews, 1988 (Box 42, Folder 12)
    - Parks-Lee, Barbara, 1987-1992; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 103, Folder 22)
    - Parris, Elliott, 1983; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 104, Folder 1)
    - Parry, Betty W., 1997; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 104, Folder 2)
    - Partlow-Myrick, Lenett Nef'faatiti, Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 104, Folder 18)
    - Partnoy, Alicia, 1986-1988; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 104, Folder 3)
    - Pate, Alexs, 1991, 1994; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 104, Folder 4)
    - Patterson, Ray, 1986-1987; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 104, Folder 5)
    - Patterson, Terrence, Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 104, Folder 6)
    - Penn, Carlotta, Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 104, Folder 7)
    - Perez, Linda Maritza, 1999; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 104, Folder 8)
    - Perkins, Stuart, Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 104, Folder 9)
    - Perry, James, Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 104, Folder 10)
    - Perry, Modupe, 1987-1990; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 104, Folder 11)
    - Perry, Richard, 1994; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 104, Folder 12)
    - Pester, Liz, 1992-1994; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 104, Folder 13)
    - Peyser, Carolyn, 1994-1995; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 104, Folder 14)
    - Phaire, Dorothy, 1994-2002; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 104, Folder 15)
    - Phillips, Carl, 1996-1997; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 104, Folder 16)
    - Phillpotts, Karl, Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 104, Folder 17)
    - Pickens, Ernestine, Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 104, Folder 19)
    - Pierson, Jennifer M., 1995; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 104, Folder 20)
    - Pietri, Pedro, 2004; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 104, Folder 21)
    - Pietri, Pedro: correspondence, articles, programs, works by, 1997 (Box 42, Folder 13)
    - Pinero, Miguel, 1981 April; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 104, Folder 22)
    - Pinsky, Robert, 1997-2000; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 104, Folder 23)
    - Pitts, Terrance, 1998; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 104, Folder 24)
    - Player, Nicole: correspondence, 1984-1990 (Box 42, Folder 14)
    - Plymell, Charles, Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 104, Folder 25)
    - Poems (Moon Sun, Xiao Min, Bei Ta), 2004; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 191, Folder 1)
    - Porter, Charlene, 1979, 1983, 1989; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 105, Folder 1 (1/2))
    - Porter, Charlene, 1979; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 105, Folder 2 (2/2))
    - Porter, Connie, 1991-1994; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 105, Folder 3)
    - Porter, Dorothy, 1972-1979; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 105, Folder 4)
    - Postell, Diane, 1982; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 105, Folder 5)
    - Powell, Daphne, 1989 January 7; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 105, Folder 6)
    - Powell, Kevin, 2002; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 105, Folder 7)
    - Pratt, Minnie Bruce, 1995; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 105, Folder 8)
    - Preiss, Sharon, 1995; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 105, Folder 9)
    - Pressley, Karlton, 1994; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 105, Folder 10)
    - Pugh, Sharon, 1992; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 105, Folder 11)
    - Queen, Daniel, 1979-1980, 1989-1990 (Box 105, Folder 12)
    - Quinn, Bill, 1995; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 105, Folder 13)
    - Rackley, Lurma, Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 105, Folder 14)
    - Rage, Patience, 1986-1987; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 105, Folder 15)
    - Rahman, Yusef, 1975; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 105, Folder 16)
    - Ramesar, Robert (Yao), 1992; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 105, Folder 17)
    - Ramsey, Kwasi H., 1998; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 105, Folder 18)
    - Randall, Dudley, 1970, 1980-1991; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 105, Folder 19)
    - Randall, Dudley: correspondence, articles, 1980 (Box 43, Folder 1)
    - Randall, Margaret: articles, biography, 1984-1987 (Box 43, Folder 2)
    - Rankine, Clandia: works by, 1993 (Box 43, Folder 3)
    - Rashad, Johari, 1982-1997; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 105, Folder 20)
    - Rasheed, 1970; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 124, Folder 15)
    - Ray, Shawn, 1989 March 16; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 106, Folder 1)
    - Ray, Walter Irving Jr., 1981, 1983, 1989, 1999-2004; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 106, Folder 2 (1/2))
    - Ray, Walter Irving Jr., 1981, 1983, 1989, 1999-2004; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 106, Folder 3(2/2))
    - Rebolledo, Francisco, 1995; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 106, Folder 4)
    - Rector, Liam, 2007; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 106, Folder 5)
    - Rector, Liam: correspondence, 1987-1988 (Box 43, Folder 4)
    - Rector, Liam: promotional material, works by, 1985-2007 (Box 43, Folder 5)
    - Reddy, T.J., 1988-1994; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 106, Folder 6)
    - Redmond, Eugene, 2007-2010; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 175, Folder 4)
    - Redmond, Eugene: Correspondence, 1983-1987; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 175, Folder 3)
    - Redmond, Eugene: Miscellaneous [1/3], 1987-2003; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 175, Folder 9)
    - Redmond, Eugene: Miscellaneous [2/3], 1986-1996; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 175, Folder 10)
    - Redmond, Eugene: Miscellaneous [3/3], 1994-2008; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 175, Folder 11)
    - Redmond, Eugene: Profiles and Articles, 1977-2013; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 175, Folder 8)
    - Redmond, Eugene: Promotional Material [1/2], 1987-1993; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 175, Folder 5)
    - Redmond, Eugene: Promotional Material [2/2], 1987-1993; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 175, Folder 6)
    - Redmond, Eugene: Works by, 2004; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 175, Folder 7)
    - Reece, Andrew, Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 106, Folder 7)
    - Reed, Ishmael: biographies, 1977 (Box 43, Folder 6)
    - Reed, Ishmael: correspondence, 1976-1985 (Box 43, Folder 7)
    - Reed, Ishmael: interviews, 1962-1986 (Box 43, Folder 8)
    - Reed, Ishmael: promotinal material, 1984-2004 (Box 43, Folder 9)
    - Reed, Ishmael: works by, 1978-1988 (Box 43, Folder 10)
    - Reed, Ishmael: Before Columbus foundation, 1981-1990 (Box 43, Folder 11)
    - Reed, Ishmael: reviews, 1972-1989 (Box 43, Folder 12)
    - Reed, Ishmael: profiles, articles, 1973-1993 (Box 43, Folder 13)
    - Reeder, Herbert, 1994; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 106, Folder 8)
    - Reetika Vazirani, 2003-2009; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 191, Folder 2)
    - Rees, Elizabeth Rose, 2002; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 106, Folder 9)
    - Regusters, Tony, Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 106, Folder 10)
    - Reinhard, Willa, 1998 December 14; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 106, Folder 11)
    - Reinhard, Willa, 2004 December 30; Series 1 Subseries 2 (Box 172, Folder 8)
    - Reker, Mary Lou: works by, 1988 (Box 43, Folder 14)
    - Renegade, D.J.: articles, programs, 1995-1999 (Box 43, Folder 15)